(Raj:)Oh, yes. Oh, okay.
(Cleaner:)Uh...
(Isabella:)Good night.
(Raj:)I don't know,
(Raj:)maybe it's the fumes
from the urinal cakes,
(Raj:)but I feel like something
is happening between us.
(Isabella:)Good night, Rajesh.
(Raj:)Okay. I'll leave.
(Raj:)But just know,
every time I come in here,
(Raj:)I'll be thinking of you.
(Sheldon:)Would you look at that?
(Sheldon:)The image we gave it
was 45% white noise,
(Sheldon:)and it still managed
to reconstruct it.
(Amy:)I've never seen results
like this before.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, we need to stop for
magnets on the way home;
(Sheldon:)this is going right
on the fridge.
(Amy:)Aren't you glad you
participated in this?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I am.
(Sheldon:)And you realize
what the next step is?
(Amy:)Set up
a second culture
(Amy:)and try to replicate
our results.
(Sheldon:)Uh, no.
(Sheldon:)We lock that door,
(Sheldon:)lower our underpants
a little and make a baby.